<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DU Marketing Student</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_open_desc">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_close_desc">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="department_name">Department of Marketing,\nUniversity of Dhaka </string>
    <string name="department_about">The Department of Marketing, one of the members of the Faculty of Business Studies, was created on 1st July, 1974. This department was established with a view to fulfilling the need for specialized education, research and training in the field of marketing. Presently, there are about 1200 students in its Bachelor, Master, M.Phil and Ph.D. programmes in the department. Since its inception, more than 3500 marketing graduates obtained degrees from this department, who cater to the growing demand for executives and trained manpower with strong skills in this specialized business area. \n The alumni of the department are holding important managerial positions in prestigious national and multinational organizations. The department offers undergraduate, graduate, M.Phil and Ph.D. programmes in Marketing. In 1978, Integrated Semester System was introduced in Bachelor and Master Degree programmes at this department. \n The research areas of the Department include Marketing Management, International Marketing, Marketing Research, Consumer Behavior, Tourism Marketing, Social Marketing, Agricultural Marketing, International Trade, Nonprofit Marketing, Entrepreneurship Development, Business Laws, Relationship Marketing Advertising, Marketing Information Systems, E-Commerce, Consumer Movement. \n The Department has a computer centre with network facility available for both faculty members and students. The Faculty Seminar Library holds the necessary text books, reference materials and periodicals in the field of marketing, business, economics and other related fields.
\n With a view to exposing the students to the out-sidethe- campus world, the department organizes guest lectures, seminars etc. inviting reputed personalities from the public and private sectors. The department occasionally organizes study tour within Bangladesh and abroad for the students of final year. \n Journal of Marketing is a half-yearly referred journal of the Department of Marketing which publishes research-based articles contributed by the academicians, educationists and professionals. \n</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="today_s_classes">Today\'s Classes</string>
    <string name="recent_notices">Recent Notices</string>
</resources>